Preliminary guide to the James Goode papers, Circa 1860-2018 MS0670.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Personal papers, 1903-2017; 1950-2014; Series 6; 4 Linear Feet
  - Family Dr. T.V. Goode I, Undated; Series 6 (Box 117, Folder 17)
- Professional papers, 1912-2018; 1964-2016; Series 7; 1.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of newsletters, magazines, organizational records, lecture notes, some research material, essays, brochures, and event pamphlets. The material dates from 1964 to 2012. This series contains the published articles by James Goode and review articles about his books. It also contains papers related to his professional work at George Mason University, the Smithsonian Institute, and the Columbia Historical Society.
  Arranged chronologically
  - Davenport College for Young Women catalogue, 1912-1913; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Articles Potomac Park, 1915; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, circa 1950-circa 1970; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Self-portrait collection, proposed tour, 1954; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia, 1965; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Goode, Univ. of VA magazine article, 1965; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Program of the inaugural ceremonies, 1965; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Goode, Virginia Cavalcade Magazine article, 1966; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous business cards, 1966-1990; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Alexandria House Tour 1965, Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Alexandria House Tour 1966, Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Alexandria House Tour 1967, Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Alexandria House Tour 1968, Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Alexandria, VA, new architecture, 1967; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Alexandria Association, 1967-1968; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - George Mason College, 1967; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - George Mason College newspaper, 1967; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - George Mason College graduation program, 1967; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous letters, 1968-1984; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Incoming letters, Smithsonian, 1970-1987; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Promotions, Smithsonian, 1970-1987; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Review, Washington Post, The Outdoor Sculpture of Washington DC, 10/1974; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Review, Architectural Record, The Outdoor Sculpture of Washington DC, 11/1974; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Article on The Outdoor Sculpture of Washington DC, Hickory Daily Record, 1974; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - "Outdoor sculpture of Washington DC", 1974; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Book review, 1975; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Charleston house tour, 1975; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - New York used book stores, 1975; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Scupture articles, 1975-2000; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Goode article, Nineteenth Century magazine, 1975; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Goode, Museum News article, 1976; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Lecture, Wilmington, NC, 1976; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Article on Smithsonian Castle gates, Washington Post, 1979; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Goode, Washington Star article, 1979; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Dinner Smithsonian Society, 1979; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Home Life, 1979; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Goode - Apt in Star, 1979; Series 7 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Goode, Capital Losses, 1979; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Goode, Smithsonian magazine article, 1979; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Publication party, Capitol Losses, 1979; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Smithsonian - sabbatical and research day, 1979-1986; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Cemeteries, DC, Washington Post article, 1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Washington Post article, Capitol Losses, 07/1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Washington Post article, Capitol Losses, 08/29/1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Lecture, Capitol Losses, 1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Washington Post article, Rhodes Tavern, 1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Washington Post article, conflict with Marian Barry, 1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Capitol Losses review, American Preservation magazine, 01/1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Gingerbread model of the Castle, 1980; Series 7 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Columbia Historical Society, Board Member (part I), 1980s; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Historical Society, Board Member (part II), 1980s; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Columbia Historical Society newsletters, 1980-1987; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Smithsonian Castle, 1981; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - White House Historical Association, 1981; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Smithsonian Gates article, 1981; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Literary Society, 1981-1998; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Article, New York Times, 1982; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Goode, Castle Gates, 1982; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Historical Society of Washington DC, Renchard Award, 1982; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - White House guide reception, 1982; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Article, Capitol Sculpture, 1982; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Alan Fern, Smithsonian, 1982; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Lecture, Cosmos Club, 1982; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Historic House Association magazine, 1983; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Renchard Prize, WP, 1983; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Smithsonian Castle, Washington Post article, 06/1984; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Article, Smithsonian "Torch", 1985; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Vandalized sculpture, 1985; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - DC Preservation League newsletter, 1986; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Washington houses article, Dossier, 1986; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - White House letter, 1986; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Notes for a Tour on the History of the Arts and Industries Building, 1986 December 05; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift of Stephen Moskey 2020 January 25 (accession 2020.007)
  - Goode, Washington Post article, 1987; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Smithsonian, Resignation, 1987; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Best Addresses, 1987; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Lost Erie, PA book, 1987; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Article, Washington Post, 1987; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Bethesda sculpture, 1987; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Cleveland Historical Society reception, 1988; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Photos, historic houses, Halifax, VA, 1988; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Museum of the Confederacy, 1988; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Goode, Washington Post article, 1989; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Article on Capitol, WETA magazine, 1989; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Articles - Aviation, 1989; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Best Addresses, review, 1989; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - National Airport essay (part I), 1989; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - National Airport essay (part II), 1989; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - National Airport history reviewed, Washington Post, 1989; Series 7 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Goode, WETA magazine article, 1989; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Smithsonian newspaper article, Best Addresses, 1989; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Article, "Museum and Arts", 1990; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - Goode, Museum and Arts magazine article, 1990; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Goode, Washingtonian magazine article, 1990; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Kiplinger Exhibition, Civil War, 1991; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Kiplinger Exhibition, US Capitol, 1993; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Kiplinger Exhibition, Then and Now, 1995; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Kiplinger Collection, catalog, 1988-1995; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Washington Times article, 02/21/1992; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - SOS - Save Outdoor Sculpture, 1992-1993; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Capital Loses, Valley View, 1994-2003; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Cemetery Exhibition, GWU Special Collections, 1994; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Article, Smithsonian "Torch", 1995; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - Article: "Capital Losses", 1995; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Smithsonian, 1995; Series 7 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Business cards for reference [1/2], 1995-2016; Series 7 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Business cards for reference [2/2], 1995-2016; Series 7 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Goode, Art News Magazine article, 1996; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Art collection, 1996; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - DC Preservation League 25th Anniversary, 1996; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Black Patriots Memorial of Revolutionary War, 1996; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Architectural Library of James M. Goode, 1997; Series 7 (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - Self-Portraits, sale, 1997; Series 7 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Doering, Ted, 2000; Series 7 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Best Addresses, new preface, 2002; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Best Addresses, lecture notes, 2003; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Lecture, Ft. McNair, 05/29/2003; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Review of Capital Losses 2nd edition, Washington Post, 07/2003; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Lecture notes, Capital Losses, 2003; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Capitol Losses, 2nd edition, 2003; Series 7 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Dunmarlin, Capital Losses, 2003; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Capital Losses, 2003; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Valley View, Capital Losses, 2003; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Lecture, Society of Architectural Historians, 06/06/2004; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Lecture, National Building Museum, 11/04//2004; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Lecture, Capital Sculpture, U.S. Capital Historical Association, 2004; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Article, "Ruthmere", 2006; Series 7 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy-Warren, flood, 2006; Series 7 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Smithsonian Gates, Seferlis Plaque, 2006; Series 7 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Sculpture article, Washington Post, 2007; Series 7 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Photography schedule for Historic Houses of Washington DC, 2010-2012; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Albert Small Washingtoniana Collection, 2004-2011; Series 7 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Albert Small Washingtoniana collection, 2011-2012; Series 7 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Washington History Vol. 24 No. 2, 2012; Series 7 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - The Portolan Issue 94, 2015; Series 7 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - The Portolan Issue 95, 2015; Series 7 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - TV program, 2017; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - GWU Museum, 2018; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Ruthmere, Board of Directors, undated; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Cemeteries outside Washington, undated; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Cemeteries outside DC, undated; Series 7 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Field notes, Undated; Series 7 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1953-2017; 1955-2017; Series 8; 18 Linear Feet
  organized into three subseries: Outgoing correspondene, Incoming correspondence and Family correspondence.
  The materials of this series include letters, postcards, and sundry other correspondence sent by and sent to James Goode. The material dates from 1953 to 2017. Most of the material is incoming correspondence. This series consists of letters, postcards, and sundry other correspondence sent to James Goode. The material dates from 1953 to 1999. This series is divided into three subseries: Outgoing correspondence, Incoming correspondence, and Family Correspondence.
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1955-1975; Series 8 Subseries 1; 1.25 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of letters, postcards, and sundry other correspondence sent by James Goode. The material dates from 1955 to 1975.
    Arranged chronologically by half-decades
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - 1958-1961, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - 1958-1965, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 1958-1965, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - 1958-1967, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - 1958-1967, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 1958-1967, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 1959-1965, 1959-65; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 1961-1962, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 1975, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Incoming correspondence, 1953-2017; 1955-2017; Series 8 subseries 2; 16.75 Linear Feet
    This series consists of letters, postcards, and sundry other correspondence sent to James Goode. The material dates from 1953 to 1999.
    Arrangtement note
    - 1953-1954, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - 1953-1954, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - 1955-1959, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - 1954-1962, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - 1958-1960, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - 1958-1960, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - 1958-1977, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - 1958-1985, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - 1957-1982, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - 1959-1995, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1965, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1964, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1995, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - 1967-1991, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - 1967-1999, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - 1969-1990, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - 1970-1974, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - 1975-1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - 1980-1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1989, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1994, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - 1995-1999, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - 1995-1999, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2015; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1958, 1997-2001; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1992; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2002; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2003; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2004; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2005; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2006; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2007; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2008; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2009; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2010; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2011; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 6)